<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Three text Passages</string>
    <string name="passage1">Text One</string>
    <string name="passage2">Text Two</string>
    <string name="passage3">Text Three</string>

    <string name="oneTitle">Rap God</string>
    <string name="one">Look, I was gonna go easy on you
Not to hurt your feelings
But I am only going to get this one chance
Something is wrong, I can feel it
(Six minutes)
Just a feeling I have got
Like somethings about to happen
But I dont know what
If that means what I think it means
We are in trouble, big trouble
And if he is as bananas as you say
Im not taking any chances
You are just what the doc ordered
Im beginnin to feel like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front to the back nod, back nod
Now, who thinks their arms are long enough
To slap box, slap box?
They said I rap like a robot, so call me Rap-bot
But for me to rap like a computer
It must be in my genes
I got a laptop in my back pocket
My penll go off when I half-cock it
Got a fat knot from that rap profit
Made a livin and a killin off it
Ever since Bill Clinton was still in office
With Monica Lewinsky feelin on his nutsack
Im an MC still as honest
But as rude and as indecent as all hell
Syllables, skill-a-holic (Kill em all with)
This flippity dippity-hippity hip-hop
You dont really wanna get into a pissin match
With this rappity brat, packin a MAC
In the back of the Ac
Backpack rap crap, yap-yap, yackety-yack
And at the exact same time
I attempt these lyrical acrobat stunts
While Im practicin that
Ill still be able to break a motherfuckin table
Over the back of a couple of faggots and crack it in half
Only realized it was ironic
I was signed to Aftermath after the fact
How could I not blow?
All I do is drop F-bombs
Feel my wrath of attack
Rappers are havin a rough time period
Heres a maxi pad
Its actually disastrously bad for the wack
While Im masterfully constructing this masterpiece as
Cause Im beginnin to feel like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front to the back nod, back nod
Now, who thinks their arms are long enough to slap box, slap box?
Let me show you maintainin this shit aint that hard, that hard
Everybody wants the key and the secret
To rap immortality like Ι have got
Well, to be truthful the blueprints
Simply rage and youthful exuberance
Everybody loves to root for a nuisance
Hit the Earth like an asteroid
Did nothing but shoot for the Moon since (Pew!)
MCs get taken to school with this music
Cause I use it as a vehicle to "bus the rhyme"
Now I lead a new school full of students
Me? Im a product of Rakim
Lakim Shabazz, 2Pac, N.W.A, Cube, hey Doc, Ren
Yella, Eazy, thank you, they got Slim
Inspired enough to one day grow up
Blow up and be in a position
To meet Run–D.M.C., induct them
Into the motherfuckin Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
Even though Ill walk in the church
And burst in a ball of flames
Only Hall of Fame Ill be inducted in
Is the alcohol of fame
On the wall of shame
You fags think its all a game
Til I walk a flock of flames
Off a plank and, tell me what in the fuck are you thinkin?
Little gay-lookin boy
So gay I can barely say it with a straight face
Lookin boy (Ha-ha!)
Youre witnessin a massacre
Like youre watching a church gathering take place, lookin boy
"Oy vey, that boys gay!"—thats all they say, lookin boy
You get a thumbs up, pat on the back
And a "way to go" from your label every day, lookin boy
Hey, lookin boy! What you say, lookin boy?
I get a "hell yeah" from Dre, lookin boy
Ima work for everything I have
Never asked nobody for shit
Get outta my face, lookin boy!
Basically, boy, youre never gonna be capable
Of keepin up with the same pace, lookin boy, cause—
Im beginnin to feel like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front to the back nod, back nod
The way Im racin around the track
Call me NASCAR, NASCAR
Dale Earnhardt of the trailer park, the White Trash God
Kneel before General Zod
This planets Krypton—no, Asgard, Asgard
So youll be Thor, Ill be Odin
You rodent, Im omnipotent
Let off, then Im reloadin
Immediately with these bombs, Im totin
And I should not be woken
Im the walkin dead, but Im just a talkin head
A zombie floatin
But I got your mom deep-throatin
Im out my Ramen Noodle
We have nothin in common, poodle
Im a Doberman, pinch yourself in the arm
And pay homage, pupil
Its me, my honestys brutal
But its honestly futile if I dont
Utilize what I do though
For good at least once in a while
So I wanna make sure somewhere in this
Chicken scratch I scribble and doodle enough rhymes
To maybe try to help get some people through tough times
But I gotta keep a few punchlines
Just in case, cause even you unsigned
Rappers are hungry lookin at me like its lunchtime
I know there was a time where once I
Was king of the underground
But I still rap like Im on my Pharoah Monch grind
So I crunch rhymes, but sometimes when you combine
Appeal with the skin color of mine
You get too big and here they come tryin
To censor you like that one line
I said on "Im Back" from The Mathers LP 1 when I
Tried to say Ill take seven kids from Columbine
Put em all in a line, add an AK-47, a revolver and a 9
See if I get away with it now
That I aint as big as I was, but Im
Morphin into an immortal, comin through the portal
Youre stuck in a time warp from 2004 though
And I dont know what the fuck that you rhyme for
Youre pointless as Rapunzel with fuckin cornrows
You write normal? Fuck being normal!
And I just bought a new raygun from the future
Just to come and shoot ya, like when Fabolous made Ray J mad
Cause Fab said he looked like a fag at Mayweathers pad
Singin to a man while he played piano
Man, oh man, that was a 24-7 special on the cable channel
So Ray J went straight to the radio station
The very next day, "Hey Fab, Ima kill you!"
Lyrics comin at you at supersonic speed (J.J. Fad)
Uh, summa-lumma, dooma-lumma, you assumin Im a human
What I gotta do to get it through to you Im superhuman?
Innovative and Im made of rubber
So that anything you say is ricochetin off of me
And itll glue to you and
Im devastating, more than ever demonstrating
How to give a motherfuckin audience
A feeling like its levitating
Never fading, and I know the haters are forever waiting
For the day that they can say I fell off, theyll be celebrating
Cause I know the way to get em motivated
I make elevating music, you make elevator music
"Oh, hes too mainstream."
Well, thats what they do when they get jealous
They confuse it
"Its not hip-hop, its pop, "—cause I found a hella way to fuse it
With rock, shock rap with Doc
Throw on "Lose Yourself" and make em lose it
"I dont know how to make songs like that
I dont know what words to use."
Let me know when it occurs to you
While Im rippin any one of these
S that versus you
Its curtains, Im inadvertently hurtin you
How many verses I gotta murder to
Prove that if you were half as nice
Your songs you could sacrifice virgins too?
Ugh, school flunky, pill junkie
But look at the accolades these skills brung me
Full of myself, but still hungry
I bully myself cause I make me do
What I put my mind to
And Im a million leagues above you
Ill when I speak in tongues
But its still tongue-in-cheek fuck you
Im drunk, so, Satan, take the fucking wheel
Ima sleep in the front seat
Bumpin Heavy D and the Boyz
Still "Chunky but Funky"
But in my head theres something
I can feel tugging and struggling
Angels fight with devils
And heres what they want from me
Theyre askin me to eliminate some of the women hate
But if you take into consideration the bitter hatred
I have, then you may be a little patient
And more sympathetic to the situation
And understand the discrimination
But fuck it, lifes handin you lemons?
Make lemonade then!
But if I cant batter the women
How the fuck am I supposed to bake them a cake then?
Dont mistake him for Satan; its a fatal mistake
If you think I need to be overseas and take a vacation
To trip a broad, and make her fall on her face and
Dont be a retard — Be a king? Think not
Why be a king when you can be a God?</string>
    <string name="twoTitle">Invisible Man</string>
    <string name="two">The stranger came early in February, one wintry day, through a biting wind and a driving snow, the last snowfall of the year, over the down, walking from Bramblehurst railway station, and carrying a little black portmanteau in his thickly gloved hand. He was wrapped up from head to foot, and the brim of his soft felt hat hid every inch of his face but the shiny tip of his nose; the snow had piled itself against his shoulders and chest, and added a white crest to the burden he carried. He staggered into the "Coach and Horses" more dead than alive, and flung his portmanteau down. "A fire," he cried, "in the name of human charity! A room and a fire!" He stamped and shook the snow from off himself in the bar, and followed Mrs. Hall into her guest parlour to strike his bargain. And with that much introduction, that and a couple of sovereigns flung upon the table, he took up his quarters in the inn.

Mrs. Hall lit the fire and left him there while she went to prepare him a meal with her own hands. A guest to stop at Iping in the wintertime was an unheard-of piece of luck, let alone a guest who was no "haggler," and she was resolved to show herself worthy of her good fortune. As soon as the bacon was well under way, and Millie, her lymphatic maid, had been brisked up a bit by a few deftly chosen expressions of contempt, she carried the cloth, plates, and glasses into the parlour and began to lay them with the utmost éclat. Although the fire was burning up briskly, she was surprised to see that her visitor still wore his hat and coat, standing with his back to her and staring out of the window at the falling snow in the yard. His gloved hands were clasped behind him, and he seemed to be lost in thought. She noticed that the melting snow that still sprinkled his shoulders dripped upon her carpet. "Can I take your hat and coat, sir?" she said, "and give them a good dry in the kitchen?"

"No," he said without turning.

She was not sure she had heard him, and was about to repeat her question.

He turned his head and looked at her over his shoulder. "I prefer to keep them on," he said with emphasis, and she noticed that he wore big blue spectacles with sidelights, and had a bush side-whisker over his coat-collar that completely hid his cheeks and face.

"Very well, sir," she said. "As you like. In a bit the room will be warmer."

He made no answer, and had turned his face away from her again, and Mrs. Hall, feeling that her conversational advances were ill-timed, laid the rest of the table things in a quick staccato and whisked out of the room. When she returned he was still standing there, like a man of stone, his back hunched, his collar turned up, his dripping hat-brim turned down, hiding his face and ears completely. She put down the eggs and bacon with considerable emphasis, and called rather than said to him, "Your lunch is served, sir."

"Thank you," he said at the same time, and did not stir until she was closing the door. Then he swung round and approached the table with a certain eager quickness.

</string>
    <string name="threeTitle">"The Colors of Animals"</string>
    <string name="three">The color of animals is by no means a matter of chance; it depends on many considerations, but in the majority of cases tends to protect the animal from danger by rendering it less conspicuous. Perhaps it may be said that if coloring is mainly protective, there ought to be but few brightly colored animals. There are, however, not a few cases in which vivid colors are themselves protective. The kingfisher itself, though so brightly colored, is by no means easy to see. The blue harmonizes with the water, and the bird as it darts along the stream looks almost like a flash of sunlight.

Desert animals are generally the color of the desert. Thus, for instance, the lion, the antelope, and the wild donkey are all sand-colored. “Indeed,” says Canon Tristram, “in the desert, where neither trees, brushwood, nor even undulation of the surface afford the slightest protection to its foes, a modification of color assimilated to that of the surrounding country is absolutely necessary. Hence, without exception, the upper plumage of every bird, and also the fur of all the smaller mammals and the skin of all the snakes and lizards, is of one uniform sand color.”

The next point is the color of the mature caterpillars, some of which are brown. This probably makes the caterpillar even more conspicuous among the green leaves than would otherwise be the case. Let us see, then, whether the habits of the insect will throw any light upon the riddle. What would you do if you were a big caterpillar? Why, like most other defenseless creatures, you would feed by night, and lie concealed by day. So do these caterpillars. When the morning light comes, they creep down the stem of the food plant, and lie concealed among the thick herbage and dry sticks and leaves, near the ground, and it is obvious that under such circumstances the brown color really becomes a protection. It might indeed be argued that the caterpillars, having become brown, concealed themselves on the ground, and that we were reversing the state of things. But this is not so, because, while we may say as a general rule that large caterpillars feed by night and lie concealed by day, it is by no means always the case that they are brown; some of them still retaining the green color. We may then conclude that the habit of concealing themselves by day came first, and that the brown color is a later adaptation.</string>
</resources>